The Amanda Steele Show. Today's goes to Vice President Kamala Harris's personal aid. So I
just want to set the stage for you. Kamala walks out to a group of folks with drums singing in
Puerto Rico. She starts clapping. While she is doing this, her aid whispers into her ear something
that very clearly makes her immediately stop clapping, which is that it was translated for
her. The song was not saying, welcome, Kamala, we like you. It was saying, why are you here? Why are
you here? Man, so that aid, you get a big up because that aid was smiling and leaned over like,
yeah, they ain't really rocking what you like that. So all right, today's goes to the organizations
that provides support dogs. Actually, just one specific person that made it a good idea to
provide Kyle Rittenhouse with a support dog. He was invited to speak at the University of Memphis
and he had the dog with him when protesters, aka students, confronted him. The dog has released
a statement listing jobs he'd rather have than work for Kyle Rittenhouse. He's down to be a poison dog
food tester, right? The dog said, I will even sit on Sarah McLachlan's lap in an ASPCA commercial.
In the arms of the angels.
We are, we are, we are.